Kael mss., 1939-2001 LMC 3004
Lilly Library
- II. Directors
  - Higgins, Colin (Box 40)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 40)
  - Hill, George Roy (Box 40)
    - Hawaii., publicity (Box 40)
  - Hill, James (Box 40)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 40)
  - Hill, Walter (Box 41)
    - Brewster's Millions., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - Crossroads., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - The Driver., notes, clippings (Box 41)
    - Extreme Prejudice., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - 48 Hrs., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 41)
    - Hard Times., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 41)
    - Johnny Handsome., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - The Long Riders., notes, clippings (Box 41)
    - Red Heat., press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - Southern Comfort., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 41)
    - Streets of Fire., (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - The Warriors., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - Materials concerning other films and Hill (Box 41)
  - Hiller, Arthur (Box 41)
    - Author! Author!, notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - The Lonely Guy., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - Love Story., notes, press release, clippings (Box 41)
    - Making Love., (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Man of La Mancha., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 41)
    - The Out-of-Towners., notes, clippings (Box 41)
    - Outrageous Fortune., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - Plaza Suite., publicity, clippings (Box 41)
    - Romantic Comedy., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 41)
    - See No Evil, Hear No Evil., press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - Silver Streak., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 41)
    - Taking Care of Business., press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - Teachers., publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 41)
    - The Tiger Makes Out., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 41)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 41)
  - Hirszman, Leon (Box 41)
    - Eles Näo Usam Black-Tie (They Don't Wear Black Tie - U.S.)., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 41)
  - Hitchcock, Alfred (Box 41)
    - Dial "M" for Murder., (see also: Box 114) (Box 41)
    - Family Plot., clippings (Box 41)
    - Frenzy., notes, printed item, clippings (Box 41)
    - Jamaica Inn., photographs (Box 41)
    - The Lady Vanishes., photographs, clippings (Box 41)
    - The Man Who Knew Too Much., (see also: Box 114) (Box 41)
    - North By Northwest., photographs, clippings (Box 41)
    - Notorious., (for poster see: Box 124) (Box 41)
    - Rear Window., notes, press release, photographs, clippings (Box 41)
    - Rope., (see also: Box 114) (Box 41)
    - The 39 Steps., photographs, clippings (Box 41)
    - To Catch a Thief., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 41)
    - Topaz., press kit, photographs, clippings (Box 41)
    - Torn Curtain., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 41)
    - Vertigo., notes, clippings (Box 41)
    - Materials concerning other films, (see also: Box 114) (Box 41)
  - Hitchcock, Alfred (cont.) (Box 42)
    - Materials concerning Hitchcock, (3 folders) (see also: Box 114) (Box 42)
    - Thirteen/WNET, New York. Publicity and stills concerning "Hitchcock: The Early Years" (Box 42)
  - Hobl, Pavel (Box 42)
    - Mate doma Iva? (Do You Keep a Lion at Home)., photographs (Box 42)
  - Hochman, Sandra (Box 42)
    - Year of the Woman., publicity, clippings (Box 42)
  - Hodges, Mike (Box 42)
    - Flash Gordon., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 42)
    - Get Carter., notes, clippings (Box 42)
    - A Prayer for the Dying., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 42)
    - Pulp., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 42)
    - The Terminal Man., notes, clippings (Box 42)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 42)
  - Hoffmann, Kurt (Box 42)
    - Bekenntnisse des Hochstaplers Felix Krull (Confessions of Felix Krull - U.S.)., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 42)
    - Wir Wunderkinder (Aren't We Wonderful? - U.S.)., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 42)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 42)
  - Holden, Lansing C. and Irving Pichel (Box 42)
    - She., photographs (Box 42)
  - Holland, Agnieszka (Box 42)
    - Bittere Ernte (Angry Harvest - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 42)
    - To Kill a Priest., credits, photographs, clippings (Box 42)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Holland (Box 42)
  - Holland, Tom (Box 42)
    - Fatal Beauty., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 42)
  - Holt, Seth (Box 42)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 42)
  - Hooper, Tobe (Box 42)
    - Lifeforce., publicity, clippings (Box 42)
    - Poltergeist., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 42)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 42)
  - Hopper, Dennis (Box 42)
    - Colors., (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - Easy Rider., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 42)
    - The Hot Spot., publicity, photographs (Box 42)
    - The Last Movie., (see also: Box 114) (Box 42)
    - Out of the Blue., notes, clippings (Box 42)
    - clippings concerning Hopper (Box 42)
  - Hough, John (Box 42)
    - Clippings concerning various films (Box 42)
  - Howard, Ron (Box 42)
    - Cocoon., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 42)
    - Gung Ho., notes, clippings (Box 42)
    - Night Shift., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 42)
    - Parenthood., press kit, clippings (Box 42)
    - Splash., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 42)
    - Willow., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 42)
    - Clippings concerning Howard (Box 42)
  - Howard, William K. (Box 42)
    - Fire Over England., (see also: Box 114) (Box 42)
  - Hudson, Hugh (Box 42)
    - Chariots of Fire., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 42)
    - Greystoke: The Legend of Tarzan, Lord of the Apes., (for pressbook see: Box 121) (Box 42)
    - Lost Angels., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 42)
    - Revolution., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 42)
  - Hughes, John (Box 42)
    - The Breakfast Club., press kit, clippings (Box 42)
    - Ferris Bueller's Day Off., notes, press release, clippings (Box 42)
    - Planes, Trains & Automobiles., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 42)
  - Hughes, John (cont.) (Box 43)
    - Sixteen Candles., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 43)
    - Uncle Buck., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 43)
    - Weird Science., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 43)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Hughes, (see also: Box 114) (Box 43)
  - Hughes, Robert (Box 43)
    - Arthur Penn, 1922-: Themes and Variants (television)., notes, press release (Box 43)
  - Hunt, Peter H. (Box 43)
    - 1776., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 43)
  - Hunter, Tim (Box 43)
    - River's Edge., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 43)
    - Sylvester., clippings (Box 43)
    - Tex., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 43)
  - Hussein, Waris (Box 43)
    - Henry VIII and His Six Wives., publicity, clippings (Box 43)
    - The Possession of Joel Delaney., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 43)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Hussein (Box 43)
  - Huston, Danny (Box 43)
    - Mr. North., (for 1988 calendar see: Box 114) (Box 43)
  - Huston, John (Box 43)
    - Across the Pacific., photographs (Box 43)
    - The African Queen., (see also: Box 114) (Box 43)
    - Annie., (3 folders) (Box 43)
    - Beat the Devil., (see also: Box 114) (Box 43)
    - The Bible: In the Beginning..., (see also: Box 114) (Box 43)
    - The Dead., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 43)
    - Fat City., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 43)
    - Freud., notes, clippings (Box 43)
    - The Life and Times of Judge Roy Bean., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 43)
    - The Maltese Falcon., program, photographs, clippings (Box 43)
    - The Man Who Would Be King., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 43)
    - Moby Dick., (see also: Box 114) (Box 43)
    - Moulin Rouge., (see also: Box 114) (Box 43)
    - Prizzi's Honor., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 43)
    - The Red Badge of Courage., (for clippings see: Box 114) (Box 43)
    - Reflections in a Golden Eye., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 43)
    - The Treasure of the Sierra Madre., (see also: Box 114) (Box 43)
    - Under the Volcano., (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Victory., notes, clippings (Box 43)
    - A Walk with Love and Death., publicity, clippings (Box 43)
    - Wise Blood., clippings (Box 43)
    - Materials concerning other films, (see also: Box 114) (Box 43)
    - Materials concerning Huston, including Materials concerning The Hustons, by Lawrence Grobel, (see also: Box 114) (Box 43)
  - Hutton, Brian G. (Box 43)
    - High Road to China., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 43)
    - Where Eagles Dare., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 43)
    - Zee and Co., publicity, clippings (Box 43)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 43)
  - Huyck, Willard (Box 44)
    - Howard the Duck., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 44)
  - Hyams, Peter (Box 44)
    - 2010., (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Capricorn One., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 44)
    - Hanover Street., notes, clippings (Box 44)
    - Outland., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 44)
    - Running Scared., (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 44)
  - Ichaso, León (Box 44)
    - Crossover Dreams., notes, press release, clippings (Box 44)
  - Ichikawa, Kon (Box 44)
    - Kagi (Odd Obsession - U.S.)., (see: Box 114) (Box 44)
    - Taiheiyo hitori-botchi (Alone on the Pacific - U.S.)., (see: Box 114) (Box 44)
  - Imamura, Shohei (Box 44)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 44)
  - Ichikawa, Kon (Box 44)
    - Biruma no tatekoto (The Burmese Harp - U.S.)., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 44)
    - Eiga joyu (Film Actress - U.S.)., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 44)
    - Kagi (Odd Obsession - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 44)
    - Kofuku (Lonely Heart - U.S.)., (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Nobi (Fires on the Plain - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 44)
    - Sasame-yuki (The Makioka Sisters - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 44)
    - Taketori monogatari (Princess from the Moon - U.S.)., publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 44)
    - Tokyo orimpikku (Tokyo Olympiad - U.S.)., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 44)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Ichikawa (Box 44)
  - Irvin, John (Box 44)
    - Champions., clippings (Box 44)
    - The Dogs of War., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 44)
    - Ghost Story., (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Hamburger Hill., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 44)
    - Next of Kin., press kit, clippings (Box 44)
    - Raw Deal., notes, color slide, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 44)
    - Turtle Diary., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 44)
  - Israel, Neal (Box 44)
    - Bachelor Party., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 44)
    - Moving Violations., publicity, clippings (Box 44)
  - Itami, Juzo (Box 44)
    - Marusa no onna (A Taxing Woman - U.S.)., clippings (Box 44)
    - Ososhiki (The Funeral - U.S.)., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 44)
    - Tampopo., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 44)
  - Ivens, Joris (Box 44)
    - Clippings concerning Ivens (Box 44)
  - Ivory, James (Box 44)
    - Autobiography of a Princess., press release, program, clippings (Box 44)
    - Bombay Talkie., publicity, clippings (Box 44)
    - The Bostonians., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 44)
    - The Guru., notes, press release (Box 44)
    - Heat and Dust., (see also: Box 114) (Box 44)
    - The Householder., photographs, clippings (Box 44)
    - Hullabaloo Over Georgie and Bonnie's Pictures., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 44)
    - Maurice., (see also: Box 114) (Box 44)
    - A Room With a View., notes, press release, clippings (Box 44)
    - Roseland., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 44)
    - Slaves of New York., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 44)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 44)
    - Materials concerning Ivory and Ismail Merchant (Box 44)
  - Jackson, Mick (Box 44)
    - Chattahoochee., press kit, clippings (Box 44)
    - L.A. Story., press kit, clippings (Box 44)
  - Jacopetti, Gualtiero (Box 44)
    - Addio zio Tom (Farewell Uncle Tom - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 44)
    - Mondo cane., notes, clippings (Box 44)
    - Notes and clippings concerning other films and Jacopetti (Box 44)
  - Jaglom, Henry (Box 44)
    - A Safe Place., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 44)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 44)
  - Jameson, Jerry (Box 44)
    - Airport '77., notes (Box 44)
    - Raise the Titanic., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 44)
  - Jancsó, Miklós (Box 44)
    - Csillagosok, katonák (The Red and the White - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 44)
    - Szegénylegények (The Hopeless Ones - U.S.)., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 44)
    - Materials concerning other films and Jancsó (Box 44)
  - Jarmusch, Jim (Box 45)
    - Down by Law., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - Mystery Train., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - Permanent Vacation., ad, clippings (Box 45)
    - Stranger Than Paradise., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 45)
  - Jarrott, Charles (Box 45)
    - Anne of the Thousand Days., publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - Lost Horizon., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - Mary, Queen of Scots., notes, program, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 45)
  - Jessua, Alain (Box 45)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 45)
  - Jewison, Norman (Box 45)
    - Agnes of God., notes, clippings (Box 45)
    - ...And Justice for All., notes, clippings (Box 45)
    - Best Friends., (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - Fiddler on the Roof., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - F.I.S.T., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - Gaily, Gaily., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - In Country., (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - In the Heat of the Night., notes, publicity, printed item, clippings (Box 45)
    - Jesus Christ Superstar., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - Moonstruck., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 45)
    - Rollerball., notes, clippings (Box 45)
    - The Russians Are Coming, the Russians Are Coming., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - A Soldier's Story., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 45)
    - Materials concerning other films and Jewison (Box 45)
  - Jodorowsky, Alejandro (Box 45)
    - Fando y Lis (Fando and Lis - U.S.)., press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 45)
    - El Topo., publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Jodorowsky (Box 45)
  - Joffé Roland (Box 45)
    - Fatman and Little Boy., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - The Killing Fields., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 45)
    - The Mission., notes, press release, photographs, clippings (Box 45)
  - Johnson, Jed (Box 45)
    - Bad., clippings (Box 45)
  - Johnson, Lamont (Box 45)
    - Cattle Annie and Little Britches., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 45)
    - The Execution of Private Slovik., notes, program, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - The Last American Hero., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - Lipstick., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
    - One on One., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 45)
    - Paul's Case., notes, clippings (Box 45)
    - Somebody Killed Her Husband., notes, publicity (Box 45)
    - Spacehunter: Adventures in the Forbidden Zone., (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - Materials concerning other films and Johnson (Box 45)
  - Johnson, Nunnally (Box 45)
    - Night People., (See also: Biberman, Howard. Salt of the Earth) (Box 45)
  - Johnston, Joe (Box 45)
    - Honey, I Shrunk the Kids., press kit (includes publicity, photograph for Tummy Trouble, directed by Rob Minkoff), clippings (Box 45)
  - Jones, Amy Holden (Box 45)
    - Love Letters., notes, clippings (Box 45)
    - Maid to Order., press release, photographs, clippings (Box 45)
    - The Slumber Party Massacre., clippings (Box 45)
  - Jones, David Hugh (Box 45)
    - Betrayal., notes, press release, clippings (Box 45)
  - Jones, Terry (Box 45)
    - Personal Services., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 45)
  - Jordan, Glenn (Box 46)
    - The Buddy System., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 46)
    - Legalese (television)., script (Box 46)
    - Mass Appeal., press kit, clippings (Box 46)
    - Only When I Laugh., clippings (Box 46)
  - Jordan, Neil (Box 46)
    - High Spirits., (for publicity see: Box 114) (Box 46)
    - Mona Lisa., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 46)
    - We're No Angels., (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 46)
  - Jouvet, Louis (Box 46)
    - Knock, ou le triomphe de la médecine (Dr. Knock - U.S.)., photographs (Box 46)
    - Photograph of Jouvet (Box 46)
  - Jutra, Claude (Box 46)
    - À tout prendre (Take It All - U.S.)., notes, press kit, photographs, clippings (Box 46)
    - By Design., notes, press release, clippings (Box 46)
    - Kamouraska., publicity, clippings (Box 46)
    - Mon oncle Antoine (My Uncle Antoine - U.S.)., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 46)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 46)
    - "Claude Jutra," by Ann Charney (Box 46)
    - Photograph and clippings concerning Jutra (Box 46)
  - Kagan, Jeremy (Box 46)
    - The Big Fix., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 46)
    - The Chosen., press kit, clippings (Box 46)
    - Heroes., (see also: Box 121) (Box 46)
    - The Journey of Natty Gann., publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 46)
    - Mr. Love., press kit (Box 46)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 46)
  - Kalatozishvili, Mikheil (Box 46)
    - Letyat zhuravli (The Cranes Are Flying - U.S.)., program, clippings (Box 46)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 46)
  - Kanew, Jeff (Box 46)
    - Tough Guys., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 46)
  - Kanin, Garson (Box 46)
    - The Great Man Votes., photographs (Box 46)
    - Clippings concerning Kanin and Ruth Gordon, (see also: Box 114) (Box 46)
  - Kaplan, Jonathan (Box 46)
    - Love Field., photographs (Box 46)
  - Karlson, Phil (Box 46)
    - Framed., clippings (Box 46)
    - Walking Tall., (2 folders) (see also: Box 114) (Box 46)
  - Kasdan, Lawrence (Box 46)
    - The Accidental Tourist., notes, press release, press kit, photographs, clippings (Box 46)
    - The Big Chill., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 46)
    - Body Heat., (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - I Love You to Death., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 46)
    - Silverado., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 46)
  - Katselas, Milton (Box 46)
    - 40 Carats., notes, clippings (Box 46)
    - Report to the Commissioner., publicity, clippings (Box 46)
    - When You Comin' Back, Red Ryder?, (3 folders) (Box 46)
    - Notes concerning other films (Box 46)
  - Kaufman, Philip (Box 46)
    - Invasion of the Body Snatchers., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 46)
    - The Right Stuff., (2 folders) (Box 46)
  - Kaufman, Philip (cont.) (Box 47)
    - The Unbearable Lightness of Being., (2 folders) (Box 47)
    - The Wanderers., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning other films and Kaufman, (see also: Box 114) (Box 47)
  - Käutner, Helmut (Box 47)
    - Der Apfel is tab (The Original Sin - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 47)
    - Des Teufels General (The Devil's General - U.S.)., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 47)
  - Kawalerowicz, Jerzy (Box 47)
    - Matka Joanna od aniolów (Joan of the Angels - U.S.)., program, clippings (Box 47)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 47)
  - Kaylor, Robert (Box 47)
    - Carny., (3 folders) (Box 47)
  - Kazan, Elia (Box 47)
    - America, America., clippings (Box 47)
    - The Arrangement., (see also: Box 114) (Box 47)
    - Baby Doll., (see also: Box 114) (Box 47)
    - Pinky., (see also: Box 114) (Box 47)
    - Splendor in the Grass., (for pressbook see: Box 121) (Box 47)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire., (see also: Box 114) (Box 47)
    - The Last Tycoon., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 47)
    - The Visitors., notes, clippings (Box 47)
    - Viva Zapata., photographs (Box 47)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Kazan, (2 folders) (see also: Box 114) (Box 47)
  - Keaton, Buster (Box 47)
    - Go West., photographs, printed item (Box 47)
    - Sherlock Jr., photographs (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning other films and Keaton, (see also: Box 114) (Box 47)
  - Keaton, Buster and John G. Blystone (Box 47)
    - Our Hospitality., program, printed item (Box 47)
  - Keaton, Buster and Clyde Bruckman (Box 47)
    - The General., photographs, program, printed item, clippings (Box 47)
  - Keaton, Diane (Box 47)
    - Heaven., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 47)
    - Clippings concerning Keaton (Box 47)
  - Kelly, Gene (Box 47)
    - Hello, Dolly!, publicity, clippings (Box 47)
    - On the Town., program, clippings (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning other films and Kelly (Box 47)
  - Kennedy, Burt (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 47)
  - Kershner, Irvin (Box 47)
    - Eyes of Laura Mars., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 47)
    - Flim-Flam Man., notes, clippings (Box 47)
    - Loving., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 47)
    - Never Say Never Again., (2 folders) (Box 47)
    - The Return of a Man Called Horse., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 47)
    - RoboCop 2., press kit, clippings (Box 47)
    - S*P*Y*S*., notes, clippings (Box 47)
    - Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back., (2 folders) (Box 47)
    - Traveling Man., notes, publicity, press kit (Box 47)
    - Up the Sandbox., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 47)
  - Kimmins, Anthony (Box 47)
    - The Captain's Paradise., photographs (Box 47)
  - King, Allan (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 47)
  - King, Henry (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 47)
  - Kinugasa, Teinosuke (Box 47)
    - Jigokumon (Gate of Hell - U.S.)., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 47)
  - Kirsanoff, Dimitri (Box 47)
    - Clippings concerning various films and Kirsanoff (Box 47)
  - Kleiser, Randal (Box 47)
    - Grease., notes, clippings (Box 47)
  - Kloves, Steven (Box 47)
    - The Fabulous Baker Boys., photographs (Box 47)
  - Kobayashi, Masaki (Box 47)
    - Kaidan (Kwaidan - U.S.)., press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 47)
    - Seppuku (Harakiri - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning other films and Kobayashi (Box 47)
  - Kollek, Amos (Box 47)
    - Forever, Lulu., press kit, clippings (Box 47)
  - Konchalovsky, Andrei (Box 47)
    - Runaway Train., notes, press release, clippings (Box 47)
    - Shy People., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 47)
    - Tango & Cash., press kit, clippings (Box 47)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 47)
  - Korda, Alexander (Box 48)
    - Private Life of Henry VIII., photographs (Box 48)
    - Rembrandt., photographs (Box 48)
  - Korty, John (Box 48)
    - Alex & the Gypsy., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 48)
    - The Autobiography of Miss Jane Pittman., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 48)
    - The Music School., notes (Box 48)
    - Funnyman., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 48)
    - Oliver's Story., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 48)
    - Materials concerning other films and Korty (Box 48)
  - Kotcheff, Ted (Box 48)